https://canari-cycling-clothing.myshopify.com/pages/privacy-policy

MY ACCOUNT
INTRODUCING FREE SHIPPING !
On All Domestic Orders Over $50 *CUSTOM NOT INCLUDED
PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
LeeMarc Industries, LLC (“Canari") is committed to protecting your privacy online. We do everything we can to make this online experience smooth and enjoyable. Gathering data regarding our customers is necessary in order to bill and ship orders with accuracy. Please read the following to understand how this information is used.
What information does CANARI collect?
CANARI asks for billing and shipping address information when a customer is ready to checkout. This address information is not, and WILL NOT, be sold to other companies to encourage more junk mail. We keep all customer information private. We also require a valid phone number. This helps us cut down on fraud and protect the online shopper.
Upon checkout, the customer is asked if they would like to be included in our mailing list for product updates. This is not required and if the customer does NOT check this box, the denial is honored. If the customer chooses NOT to be included, they will not receive newsletters or mass email from us. If they do choose to be added to our mailing list, either via ordering or the subscribe box in the sidebar, they can easily unsubscribe by following the instructions at the bottom of our newsletter.
What are "cookies" and how do we use them?
CANARI uses cookies to track your current shopping cart. Cookies are small bits of data that are sent to your browser and stored on your hard drive. We require that cookies have been turned on (in your browser) in order to use this site. We also collect IP addresses and browser info in order to report on demographics and technology used by our visitors.
What do we do with the information we collect?
We use it to ship your order. That's all.
With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?
CANARI does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others.
What if I want to change my account information?
You can change your account information at any time by logging in to your account. Once you are signed in, click on "edit account details" to make changes to your account details. To change your saved addresses, you may make these alterations at the bottom of your account page.
Your consent
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by CANARI.com as outlined in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.
This version of the Canari Privacy Policy is effective February 1, 2015.
